Previously on Pretty Little Liars.
Is this what you're looking for?
Ezra is taking on these big
responsibilities. And he needs a job.
The park rangers found a body.
It was Toby.
No, Spence, it wasn't.
Will you just tell me that what
I saw tonight wasn't real?
Please, tell me.
I'm here to pick up Malcolm.
Your friend picked me up instead.
She said her name was Alison.
They just found a body tonight.
 Where?
Exactly where Spencer said it was.
I don't think that
I can do this, anymore.
Look at all that's happened
since you turned me down on
our little drive up the Mountain.
You don't have to ask
me again, Mona. I'm in.
Maybe she's just
as nervous about
seeing us as we are
about seeing her.
Guys, she's the exact same Spencer
that we saw last week.
No, the Spencer we saw in Radley
was not the Spencer I know.
That was before.
Em, we're not just here for
her, we're for you, too.
Do we talk about him?
Do we bring it up?
I don't want to say anything
that could put her back there.
I know they said
they found Toby,
but they sent that second
body to the state coroner
for a reason. I mean,
maybe there's hope.
You know how I feel about hope.
Breeds eternal misery.
We lost Toby a long time ago.
We just didn't know it.
Oh, you've got to love
the Hastings.
I just get released
from a mental hospital,
and they welcome my friends
with tea and crumpets.
What's the difference
between a crumpet
and an English muffin?
Hanna, does it matter?
I'm just making conversation.
An English muffin is a baked bread.
It's made of dough.
And a crumpet is a griddle cake
made of batter.
How are you, Spence?
I'm all right.
You know, you don't have to
pretend to be okay for us.
Yeah, if this was
the act you had to pull off
to get out of there, then...
Do you remember when you were
in the light house, Emily?
And you had to make
that choice?
It was either him or you?
I wasn't as strong as you were.
When I saw Toby in the woods,
like that, I just gave up.
So what changed?
You seem like you're
back to yourself.
I decided I didn't want
to be victim any more.
That's not who I am.
Here.
What's this?
My parents told all of
their friends that I went
to Radley for exhaustion,
so they want to throw
a soiree to make sure
that everybody knows that
I'm all better now.
Could really use some support.
Can you guys please come?
Of course.
Sure.
Yeah, you know
we'd do anything for you.
I'm counting on that.
♪ I'm going to send you
the devil's love song ♪
♪ I'm going to break the news
to you my love ♪
♪ I'm going to send you
the devil's love song ♪
♪ You're going to learn to play
♪ I'm going to sing it to you
girls and boys ♪
♪ You're going to learn to play
the devil's love song ♪
We like your plan.
You'll get your reward Friday.
Those bitches are finally
going to get what they deserve.
♪ It's where this one
you save ♪
♪ Got a locket,
in your pocket ♪
♪ Taking this one
to the grave ♪
♪ Ever show you
that I know you ♪
♪ Won't tell what I said ♪
♪ 'Cause two can
keep a secret ♪
♪ If one of them is dead ♪
Did Malcolm tell you
what she looked like?
No, he just said she
was a friend of mine,
and her name was Alison.
That's all I know.
Well, look... you have to
talk to him, find out more.
Yeah, like did she have dark
hair, horns, and a tail?
Guys, no, we are not using
Malcolm to get to Mona.
You know, the last time
I saw Ezra
I could hardly face him.
All we have to do is show
Mona's picture to the kid.
He'll confirm that Mona took him
and the cops will
take our lulu-head
back to the nut farm.
Hanna.
Sorry, Spence.
My bad.
I don't know,
it seems like a really
bold move for Mona.
The risk being seen like that?
What are you saying, Spence?
It feels desperate.
Like maybe she's
trying to get caught.
Okay, well, Malcolm
is off limits, okay?
Gotta get to class.
I can use some extra money.
Did you not just hear Aria?
Em, kids love me.
I'll make a game out of it.
Hey, Emily.
Hey.
What-uh-what are you doing here?
Our coach arranged
for us to practice
here this morning.
But I say if it's water,
it's wet, right?
A pool's a pool.
I don't think we've met.
Uh, Shana, this is Spencer.
Uh, you swim for Oakwood?
Amongst other things.
Will you be at the meet?
Yeah. Wouldn't miss it.
I'll look for you.
Good luck, Emily.
You, too.
I hate her.
Why?
Because she flirts with
everyone but me.
Shana's bad news.
Wherever she goes,
trouble follows.
Well, it was great seeing you.
Take care.
Hey.
Did you have another interview?
Yeah, they called this morning.
Well, that's good.
Probably means that
they're interested
in having you back.
I don't think it's
going to work out for me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You said you were going
to make it all go away.
I'm worried that the police
have evidence.
Look, I need to see you today.
I've got to go.
Bye.
I just got off
the phone with your mom.
Did you know that Ezra
was applying for
a teaching job
at Rosewood High?
Yeah, he applied for a job
subbing in the district.
Listen, your mom and I
recognise that Ezra
needs to find a way
to support his son.
But he cannot teach in Rosewood if
you two are still seeing each other.
You're leaving us no choice...
Dad, slow down, okay.
He's not getting the job.
He was offered the position
this morning, Aria.
Ezra asked for the day to
decide if he wants to take it.
So, Aria didn't tell me that you
were interested in the job.
Oh, well, I didn't tell
her because I didn't want
to feel pressured if you
gave me the gig. Ahh.
Thank you.
So, Malcolm's seven, right?
 Mm-hmm.
What's he into?
Fast cars and fast girls?
It's a joke.
He's into trains.
Oh! Well, all aboard the Hanna express.
Um, do you have
a resume, or anything?
Honestly, I haven't
baby sat since I was 15.
But my mom's in New York,
Caleb's out of town,
so, I have a lot
of time to kill.
And I could use
the extra money.
Okay. I have an
appointment tonight,
so, if you're free,
we can give it a test run.
See if it's a good fit.
Well, it will be, promise.
I've missed you.
They'll all be together
this Friday.
You know what you need to do.
Yeah. What did the
doctor say about your eyes?
Um, I'll have good days
and bad days.
Eventually they'll all be bad.
On your darkest days,
you know I'll be here for you.
Hey.
Is everything okay?
Why didn't you tell me that
they offered you the job?
'Cause I don't think
I'm going to take it.
And I didn't think you should share
in the burden of that decision.
You need a job, Ezra.
Yeah,
but you know what would
happen to us if I end up
back at Rosewood.
Things are different now.
People know about us.
Hey, don't... don't cry.
Don't cry.
We're okay.
No, we're not.
Nothing about
us feels right anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I want to fix this.
I know.
I know, but you can't.
Okay, we've been chasing
after what we used to have
ever since you found out
about Malcolm, but...
I just don't...
I don't think that
we can ever get that back.
Things aren't easy,
but they can still be good.
It shouldn't be this hard.
If you're not happy anymore...
You know, that's
what matters most to me.
Hey, I love you just
as much as I always have.
And that's why I want you
to take this job.
Aria, wait, wait.
I love you.
♪ So full so empty still ♪
♪ You leave me wanting ♪
♪ Oh tell where'd you go ♪
♪ Don't be invisible ♪
Evening, ma'am.
♪ Save me ♪
♪ Go on break ♪
♪ the glass ♪
♪ Take me ♪
It's seat yourself,
Pretty Eyes.
♪ I've nowhere else to go ♪
Hanna got the job.
I know.
Spencer.
When I was in Radley,
Mona told me that you
were alive.
I wanted to believe her,
but until now...
Back in the woods,
was that you?
Were you a part of it?
Mona told me after.
And you let me believe
that you were dead?
Everything I've done,
was so I could protect you.
I want to believe that.
Let me take you somewhere safe.
Does Mona know you're here?
No.
She told me you'd
be there Friday.
That you'd be my reward
for delivering the girls.
How'd you find me?
She left me alone in her lair.
I kidnapped a seven-year-old.
I'm the reason that Aria
and Ezra broke up.
So, I've earned her trust.
It's not safe for you
to be here.
I stopped worrying about me
a long time ago.
What we had was real.
I've been pretending to work
with Mona
so I could keep you safe.
I need you to believe me.
And I need you to follow me.
Do want to play a game?
Come on, it'll be fun.
My dad said I can
watch cartoons.
Fine.
But you should know that
watching TV rots your brain.
It's your choice if you want
to grow up to be stupid.
Just sayin'.
Okay, let's play "Guess Who."
I'll show you a picture
of a person,
and you tell me if you know them.
Okay.
That's Aria.
See. You're good at this.
Okay.
Do you know her?
She didn't take you
to the carnival?
I went with Aria's friend,
Alison.
Is this Alison?
Nope.
What about this?
What about this person?
That's a boy.
I am going to go call
my friend really quick.
Can I play a game
on your phone?
Sure.
Hey.
I struck out.
He's seven.
Maybe he's confused.
Hanna.
I gotta call you back.
I don't understand, they have
the tapes and that can't...
no, I do understand,
but those bitches
are going to be at
the lodge at nine.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
Doesn't look
like anybody lives here.
I shuffle between a few motels.
Mona doesn't know
about this one.
And red coat?
The only thing I know about red
coat is that she's in charge.
I know.
You still don't trust me.
Look, I understand why
you've been helping Mona.
I made the same decision.
But if I saw you hurting,
the way I know you saw me...
Toby.
No wonder I was a fat kid.
When my dad cheated on my mom
and left us to
start a new family,
I had a box of these a night.
But I would get some peanut
butter and that frosting in
a can and have a party.
Alison's right here.
What?
She's in this picture.
I don't remember that.
It just popped up.
That can't be who you saw.
That's Aria's friend, Alison.
No, Malcolm, that girl's...
I remember her pretty hair.
That's her, Hanna.
With the blue shirt.
Spencer?
That's Allison.
I mean he said she was the girl
in the blue shirt.
This is crazy.
And you're saying,
that Shana knows Jenna.
And that the both of them are
meeting up with Melissa?
This is crazier than crazy.
I mean, Radley's
looking better every day.
I'm actually ready to check in.
We're going to figure it out.
I've already got it
figured out.
Spencer's part of the A-team. Game over.
Today it's me and Ezra. Tomorrow
it'll be you and Caleb.
And then it's going
to be your turn Emily,
so get ready to say
goodbye to Paige,
'cause I promise you, A's
going to take her from you.
Why would Spencer
do this to us?
Guys, I don't believe
for one second
that Spencer's on the A-team.
Okay, if she is
working with Mona
then there has to be more
to the story.
We don't know what happened in Radley.
But Spencer went in
there at rock bottom. And she
came out like a shiny new penny.
Are you thinking
shock treatment?
No. No, I'm saying that Mona
spent a lot of time in Radley.
And maybe she made
some friends.
And maybe Spencer talked
to some of those friends.
Mona asked Spencer
to join the A-team
on the night of
the masquerade ball.
Did Spencer
finally take her up on it?
Yeah, but why now?
There's a way to prove
that Spencer's still with us,
and if Mona's watching,
it won't put Spencer at risk.
Really, Hanna? You're in
the mood for a dance party?
Look, a was everywhere before
Spencer joined the A-team.
Do you really think
we're meeting in secret?
♪ I've been
out on that open road ♪
♪ You can be my full-time daddy ♪
♪ White and gold ♪
♪ Singing blues has
been gettin' old ♪
♪ You can be my full-time baby ♪
♪ hot or cold ♪
♪ Don't break me down ♪
♪ I've been drivin' too long ♪
♪ with one pretty song ♪
♪ I hear the birds
on the summer breeze ♪
♪ I drive fast,
I am alone in the night ♪
♪ Been tryin' hard not to get
into trouble ♪
♪ But I, I've got a war
in my mind ♪
♪ So, I just ride ♪
♪ just ride ♪
♪ I just ride ♪
Aria.
I took the job.
You remember what you
said at Ali's funeral?
You were right. There never
was a happy ending for us.
You know, this doesn't
have to be forever.
You're graduating
in seven months.
And I wish that
I could hold onto that.
But, it's too hard.
I need to move on,
and so do you.
Bye, Ezra.
And what a win for the Red Devils!
What is this?
You followed me here,
that means you don't
know who she is, either.
And if you don't
know who she is,
that means you're
still one of us.
Look Spencer...
Whatever it is,
no matter how deep
you're into this,
you know that you can
tell us the truth, right?
We want to help you.
Mona came to see me at Radley.
And when I found Toby
in the woods,
she'd planned the whole thing.
She wanted to break
me so that she could
put me back together.
Like her own humpty dumpty.
So, Mona made you an offer
you couldn't refuse?
She told me that
Toby was still alive.
Toby's alive?
And it's true.
It's true, he's been
working with Mona because
he found out about red coat
and Mona's the only person
who knows who she is.
And you've seen him?
Yeah.
Last night.
He's on our side.
You guys, he always was.
But this party tomorrow, it's a set-up.
Red coat just wants us all
to be together.
Why? What's she gonna do to us?
I don't know.
But we're not going
to let it happen.
Okay, whatever it is,
we're one step ahead of her,
finally, and there are
two of us on the inside.
And when were you going
to clue us in on
your double agent status,
Nikita?
I'm the one who sent you
the picture of me and Ali.
And you did exactly what
I needed you to do.
Because Mona watches
my every move.
You've found a way to get to me
without her knowing about it.
So, instead of red coat
waiting for us tomorrow,
we'll be waiting for her.
And if we're lucky,
this will all be over with.
Luck won't have
anything to do with it.
All right, good morning.
My name is Mister Fitz.
And I'm back as
your substitute teacher.
Uh, if we open up to Chapter One,
we'll find out why Hemingway said,
"All things truly wicked,
start from innocence."
It's perfect timing, actually.
I need a pick-me-up.
That place is really nice.
It's the Hastings. Were you
expecting "donuts and dogs"?
How can you afford
new miu mius?
Oh! I borrowed them.
The store gives full
refunds for returns.
That's if you don't wear them.
Doesn't say that
on the receipt.
They're running late.
How late?
They're on their way.
That's all I know.
She's expecting all
of you to be here.
And we will be.
You have no idea what she's
capable of, Spencer.
Trust me. You don't
want to disappoint her.
I saw them getting ready.
And I have the video
you asked for.
They don't suspect anything.
You guys, I'm serious about not
taking back those shoes.
Hanna, quiet!
We've got to get inside
before red coat shows up.
If she knows we're onto her,
we'll never find out who she is.
Are we sure we trust Toby?
Spencer does.
Do we have a choice?
It's all according to plan.
How far away are you?
It's safe for you to land.
It's finally about to end.
You're getting what
you've always wanted.
She doesn't know
the others aren't here yet.
I told you, they're coming.
Why don't we for a walk
while we wait?
I'll take care of Spencer.
Toby?
I know how you feel, Spencer.
It sucks to be lied to.
Get up.
I believed you.
I said get up!
You won't get away with this.
I'd say "Watch me," but you
won't be here to see it.
If something goes wrong,
you know what you need to do.
Going somewhere?
You're making a terrible
mistake.
That's not how we see it.
Because you don't see.
You have know idea
what's going on here.
We know enough.
Who is that?
Get to the plane.
Wait, Toby!
Be careful. Remember why
we're here, Spencer.
You see her.
She doesn't see you.
What have you done?
Mona, try your phone.
Nothing.
How can you not have a signal?
We saw you make a call.
It's her. Don't you get it?
She can do anything.
She's everywhere
and she's nowhere.
Come on, let's get out of here.
It's locked!
We're gonna die.
We're all going to burn.
Shut up, Mona!
I'm never going
to know who she was.
What did you just say?
Red coat.
I don't know who she is either.
Are you kidding?
You guys, we have
to get out of here.
Ali?
Did anyone see her?
See who?
Alison. She pulled me out of
there. She pulled us all out.
No, you're hallucinating.
She was here.
I swear it.
Ali's dead.
I saw her, too.
So did I.
Ali is red coat.
So all of this started
when you were at Radley?
I made a deal with the devil.
And she gave me a way in
and out of that place.
At first it was fun,
having a partner.
But then the game changed.
She stole you from me.
So what happened that night?
Were you there at the cemetery?
Did you drug me?
Did you take Ali's body?
I don't know who drugged you.
But I was at the cemetery
and so was red coat.
How could you
not see who it was?
She was wearing a mask.
She looked just like Ali.
That's probably
what happened tonight.
It wasn't Ali.
It was a mask.
Guys?
Wait, is that?
Somebody pulled it out
of the lake.
Think this through, Ashley.
How do you live with yourself?
We're not done here.
Hey!
We've have to get
this out of here.
Wait! There's more.
It's Jenna.
And Shana?
They know Wilden?
Guys...
Look at the trunk.
You're mine now.
Kisses...
A.